Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Is Mr. Gu Hou Ze here?
هل السيد جو هو زي هنا؟
Do you have an appointment?
هل لديك موعد؟
Do we look sick?
هل نبدو مرضى؟
It's you. You look sick.
أنت تبدو مريضًا.
Let's meet at the same time next week.
دعونا نلتقي في نفس الوقت الأسبوع المقبل.
Okay. Thank you, Dr. Gu.
حسنًا. شكرًا لك، دكتور جو.
How may I help you?
كيف يمكنني مساعدتك؟
Are you Gu Hou Ze?
هل أنت قو هو زي؟
Yes, that's me.
نعم، هذا أنا.
Don't you think the debt should be settled?
ألا تعتقد أن الدين يجب أن يتم تسويته؟
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
أنا لست متأكدًا مما تتحدث عنه.
Goodness.
الخير.
Isn't your name all over these?
أليس اسمك موجود في كل مكان؟
Call Ms. Fan first.
اتصل بالسيدة فان أولاً.
I think a Ms. Fan borrowed money from you under my name.
أعتقد أن السيدة فان اقترضت منك أموالاً باسمي.
But I'm not sure about the actual situation.
ولكنني لست متأكدًا من الوضع الفعلي.
[Episode 5: Are we sick or is love twisted?]
[الحلقة 5: هل نحن مرضى أم أن الحب ملتوٍ؟]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
- Hello, is this Miss Fan Yue Jiao? - Yes.
- مرحبًا، هل هذه الآنسة فان يوي جياو؟ - نعم.
I'm Commissioner Chen from Fubon Bank's Foreign Exchange Department.
أنا المفوض تشين من قسم الصرف الأجنبي في بنك فوبون.
Your foreign currency transaction has been processed.
لقد تمت معالجة معاملة العملة الأجنبية الخاصة بك .
Account details will be sent to your email shortly.
سيتم إرسال تفاصيل الحساب إلى بريدك الإلكتروني قريبًا.
Please check it. Thank you.
يرجى التحقق من ذلك. شكرًا لك.
Okay, thank you.
حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
I'll contact you if I have any questions.
سأتواصل معك إذا كان لدي أي أسئلة.
I've compiled the results of the past two years' art auctions.
لقد قمت بتجميع نتائج المزادات الفنية للعامين الماضيين.
I found that this kind of abstract painting
لقد وجدت أن هذا النوع من الرسم التجريدي
is starting to attract collectors.
بدأت تجذب هواة الجمع.
Also, the Japanese New Generation artists you've bought and sold
أيضًا، فناني الجيل الجديد اليابانيين الذين اشتريتهم وبعتهم
all seem to be of this type.
يبدو أن جميعها من هذا النوع.
Why don't you talk to them again?
لماذا لا تتحدث معهم مرة أخرى؟
See if there are any new works.
انظر إذا كان هناك أي أعمال جديدة.
Okay.
تمام.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Why don't we end here for today?
لماذا لا ننتهي هنا اليوم؟
Mr. Zhan wants to have dinner with you and asked me to book a restaurant.
السيد تشان يريد تناول العشاء معك وطلب مني أن أحجز مطعمًا.
What kind of food do you want to eat?
ما نوع الطعام الذي تريد أن تأكله؟
I'm going to the restroom.
سأذهب إلى الحمام.
Director Qian, Vice President. You're here to see the paintings, too?
المديرة تشيان، نائبة الرئيس. هل أتيتِ لرؤية اللوحات أيضًا؟
[Hou Ze]
[امسكهم]
Pan Xin Tong.
بان شين تونغ.
You're taking huge strides.
أنت تتخذ خطوات كبيرة.
Wow.
رائع.
You're so elegant now.
أنت أنيقة جداً الآن.
I guess you've dipped your toes into art sales and acquisitions, huh.
أعتقد أنك قد غطست أصابع قدميك في مبيعات وشراء الأعمال الفنية، أليس كذلك.
It's no surprise.
ليس مفاجئا.
You're with Mr. Qian now.
أنت مع السيد تشيان الآن.
It's good for you to improve yourself.
من الجيد أن تعمل على تحسين نفسك.
Excuse me, Vice President. I have to go.
عذراً، نائب الرئيس، عليّ الذهاب.
Don't be in a rush.
لا تستعجل .
I'm Yi Fu's uncle, after all.
أنا عم يي فو، بعد كل شيء.
Here's the thing.
هذا هو الشيء.
If there's anything between you and Yi Fu,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء بينك وبين يي فو،
you can share it with me.
يمكنك مشاركتها معي.
I have a lot of tips for you.
لدي الكثير من النصائح لك.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Often, when it comes to relationships...
في كثير من الأحيان، عندما يتعلق الأمر بالعلاقات...
Vice President Qian, what's the matter?
نائب الرئيس تشيان، ما الأمر؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
I'm just concerned about my employee...
أنا فقط أشعر بالقلق بشأن موظفي...
my ex-employee's life.
حياة موظفي السابق.
So, she won't be exploited by her current boss.
لذلك، لن يتم استغلالها من قبل رئيسها الحالي.
Don't worry, Vice President Qian.
لا تقلق، نائب الرئيس تشيان.
She's doing very well here.
إنها تقوم بعمل جيد جدًا هنا.
Glad her talent hasn't been doomed to obscurity at your place.
يسعدني أن موهبتها لم تصبح طي النسيان في مكانك.
We're done here, right?
لقد انتهينا هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Pan Xin Tong.
بان شين تونغ.
Director Qian is looking for you.
المخرج تشيان يبحث عنك.
What's going on? Let me see.
ماذا يحدث؟ دعني أرى.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let go! Let go of him!
دعه يذهب! دعه يذهب!
Let go of him!
اتركه!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Kill him!
اقتله!
Are you two going to pay the 40 million?
هل ستدفعان الـ40 مليونًا؟
Why are you still standing there? Get lost!
لماذا لا تزال واقفًا هناك؟ اغرب عن وجهتك!
Why did you borrow so much money?
لماذا اقترضت هذا القدر الكبير من المال؟
Oh my.
أوه يا إلهي.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Those punks didn't know better and got you bruised.
هؤلاء الأشرار لم يعرفوا الأفضل وتسببوا في إصابتك بكدمات.
Please don't hold a grudge.
من فضلك لا تحمل ضغينة.
I don't have that much cash right now.
ليس لدي الكثير من المال الآن.
You need to give me some time.
يجب أن تعطيني بعض الوقت.
Look at what you're saying.
أنظر إلى ما تقوله.
You have to show your sincerity today.
يتوجب عليك أن تظهر صدقك اليوم.
How much do you need today?
كم تحتاج اليوم؟
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Miss, are you paying for him?
آنسة، هل تدفعين له؟
How much?
كم ثمن؟
Two million.
مليونين.
Did you get in touch with Ms. Fan?
هل تواصلت مع السيدة فان؟
No, but I texted her.
لا، لكنني أرسلت لها رسالة نصية.
I'll try again.
سأحاول مرة أخرى.
I'll find a way to pay you back the two million.
سأجد طريقة لسداد المليونين لك.
Why did you borrow so much money from loan sharks?
لماذا اقترضت هذا القدر الكبير من المال من المرابين؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Ms. Fan borrowed it under my company's name.
لقد استعارتها السيدة فان باسم شركتي.
I'm the person in charge, so they came to collect from me.
أنا الشخص المسؤول، لذلك جاءوا ليجمعوا مني.
Cindy.
سيندي.
Help me check how much money we have left in the company.
ساعدني في التحقق من مقدار الأموال المتبقية لدينا في الشركة.
And the loans, too.
والقروض أيضا
Didn't we disagree on increasing the capital before?
ألم نختلف على زيادة رأس المال من قبل؟
So, you didn't know Ms. Fan borrowed money?
إذن، لم تكن تعلم أن السيدة فان اقترضت المال؟
Don't let the other shareholders know yet.
لا تدع المساهمين الآخرين يعرفون ذلك بعد.
Just find it and give it to me.
فقط ابحث عنه وأعطني إياه.
That's all for now.
هذا كل شئ في الوقت الراهن.
By the way, why did you come looking for me today?
بالمناسبة، لماذا أتيت تبحث عني اليوم؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Director Qian, were you looking for me?
المخرج تشيان، هل كنت تبحث عني؟
I don't like to beat around the bush.
أنا لا أحب أن أطيل الحديث.
I'll get straight to the point.
سأذهب مباشرة إلى النقطة.
Please leave Yi Fu.
من فضلك اترك يي فو.
Have you asked Yi Fu for his opinion?
هل سألت يي فو عن رأيه؟
I've seen a lot of people like you.
لقد رأيت الكثير من الناس مثلك.
Stop pretending in front of me.
توقف عن التظاهر أمامي.
People like me?
الناس مثلي؟
You know what I mean.
أنت تعرف ما أعنيه.
Why do you have to humiliate yourself?
لماذا عليك أن تهين نفسك؟
Is this going to unfold like a TV drama?
هل سيصبح هذا الأمر مثل الدراما التلفزيونية؟
Are you going to write me a check for millions to get me to leave Yi Fu?
هل ستكتب لي شيكًا بملايين الدولارات لتجعلني أترك يي فو؟
I'm not as stupid as an idol drama heroine.
أنا لست غبية مثل بطلة الدراما الأصنام.
I might really take it.
ربما سأأخذه حقا.
You must think you're special.
يجب أن تعتقد أنك مميز.
All of Yi Fu's girlfriends thought so, too.
جميع صديقات يي فو اعتقدن ذلك أيضًا.
But the result has been the same.
ولكن النتيجة كانت نفسها.
If you don't break up now,
إذا لم تنفصل الآن،
you'll still be dumped within three months.
سيتم تركك بعد ثلاثة أشهر.
By then, you'll only hurt yourself more.
بحلول ذلك الوقت، سوف تؤذي نفسك أكثر.
You should know.
ينبغي عليك أن تعرف.
Yi Fu has never been in a relationship for more than three months.
لم يكن يي فو في علاقة لمدة تزيد عن ثلاثة أشهر.
What makes you think you'll be any different?
ما الذي يجعلك تعتقد أنك ستكون مختلفًا؟
This is between him and me.
هذا بيني وبينه.
We'll handle it ourselves.
سوف نتعامل مع الأمر بأنفسنا.
As for you, your task should be
أما بالنسبة لك، فيجب أن تكون مهمتك
to listen to your son more.
للاستماع إلى ابنك أكثر.
Respect him.
احترمه.
Are you lecturing me?
هل أنت تحاضرني؟
I wouldn't dare.
لا أجرؤ على ذلك.
If that's all you want to talk about,
إذا كان هذا كل ما تريد التحدث عنه،
I won't waste your time.
لن أضيع وقتك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine, but I was so scared.
أنا بخير، ولكنني كنت خائفة جدًا.
They even hit Dr. Gu.
حتى أنهم ضربوا الدكتور جو.
They hit Dr. Gu?
هل ضربوا الدكتور جو؟
Where's Dr. Gu?
أين الدكتور جو؟
- Dr. Gu left. - Where did he go?
- غادر الدكتور جو. - إلى أين ذهب؟
There was a Ms. Zhou Xiao Qi who came for counseling.
كانت هناك السيدة تشو شياو تشي التي جاءت للحصول على المشورة.
She came when Dr. Gu was beaten up.
لقد أتت عندما تعرض الدكتور جو للضرب.
She said she could help pay the interest first.
قالت إنها تستطيع المساعدة في سداد الفائدة أولاً.
Dr. Gu left with her just now.
لقد غادر الدكتور جو معها للتو.
Zhou Xiao Qi?
تشو شياو تشي؟
If it wasn't for her today, do you think those gangsters would've let me off so easily?
لو لم تكن هي اليوم، هل تعتقد أن هؤلاء العصابات كانوا سيتركونني بسهولة؟
Answer me first. Why are you still involved with her?
أجبني أولاً. لماذا لا تزال على علاقة بها؟
- What other secrets do you have? - Answer me first!
- ما هي الأسرار الأخرى التي لديك؟ - أجبني أولاً!
How much more did you borrow?
كم أقترضت أكثر؟
Coincidentally, she came to your rescue?
وبالمصادفة، جاءت لإنقاذك؟
You wouldn't let me invest more, so I took out a loan.
لم تسمح لي باستثمار المزيد، لذلك أخذت قرضًا.
- The bank refused, so I took a private loan. - Have you thought they'd harass the clinic?
- رفض البنك، فأخذت قرضًا خاصًا. - هل فكرت أنهم سوف يضايقون العيادة؟
I've never let you worry about money.
لن أتركك أبدًا تقلق بشأن المال.
- How are we going to run the business now? - You'll be a famous doctor and writer.
- كيف سندير العمل الآن؟ - سوف تصبح طبيبًا وكاتبًا مشهورًا.
- And then you'll have affairs? - Have you ever thought about that?
-وبعد ذلك سيكون لديك علاقات؟ -هل فكرت في هذا من قبل؟
There's such a big trench now.
هناك خندق كبير الآن.
Have you thought about how to fix it?
هل فكرت في كيفية إصلاح الأمر؟
How are you going to pay back the money?
كيف سوف تقوم بسداد الأموال؟
I'll be honest with you.
سأكون صادقا معك.
When I borrowed the money, I didn't plan to pay it back.
عندما اقترضت المال، لم يكن لدي أي نية لسداده.
I've wired the money overseas.
لقد قمت بتحويل الأموال إلى الخارج.
I've transferred it overseas.
لقد نقلته إلى الخارج.
Fan Yue Jiao, are you crazy?
فان يو جياو، هل أنت مجنون؟
Let's go to New Zealand together.
دعونا نذهب إلى نيوزيلندا معًا.
The money is enough for us to live on.
المال يكفينا للعيش.
Are you saying we should give up everything here
هل تقول أننا يجب أن نتخلى عن كل شيء هنا؟
and go live in New Zealand?
وأذهب للعيش في نيوزيلندا؟
What are you thinking?
ماذا تفكر؟
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
You're the crazy one.
أنت المجنون.
- You can't leave her. - Don't drag her into everything.
- لا يمكنك تركها. - لا تجرها إلى كل شيء.
She's the reason we're in this situation.
إنها السبب في وصولنا إلى هذا الوضع.
You know very well what our relationship is like.
أنت تعرف جيدًا ما هي علاقتنا.
Okay.
تمام.
It's fine if you don't want to go to New Zealand.
لا بأس إذا كنت لا ترغب في الذهاب إلى نيوزيلندا.
But you know what's going on now, right?
لكنك تعلم ما يحدث الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Those loan sharks will make the news.
سوف يظهر هؤلاء المرابون في الأخبار.
You'll be a joke, ruined.
سوف تكون نكتة، مدمرة.
Let's see what you can do then.
دعونا نرى ما يمكنك فعله إذن.
Yue Jiao.
يو جياو.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
لقد فعلت هذا عمدا، أليس كذلك؟
Wire the money back.
قم بتحويل الأموال مرة أخرى.
You promised me we'd go to New Zealand together.
لقد وعدتني بأننا سنذهب إلى نيوزيلندا معًا.
This time, we can finally go together.
هذه المرة، يمكننا أخيرا أن نذهب معا.
Spare me, please.
أرجوك أنقذني.
You love me.
كنت تحبني.
You've just temporarily forgotten.
لقد نسيت الأمر مؤقتًا.
Here you go. This is for you.
تفضل. هذا لك.
Do you want to order anything else?
هل تريد أن تطلب أي شيء آخر؟
We have a secret dish here.
لدينا طبق سري هنا.
It's not on the menu.
إنه ليس في القائمة.
Chicken Feet Jelly.
جيلي أقدام الدجاج.
Are you tired of spicy hot pot?
هل سئمت من الطبق الساخن الحار؟
You were much more excited last time you had it.
لقد كنت أكثر حماسًا في المرة الأخيرة.
I'm not hungry.
أنا لست جائعا.
You're not hungry?
أنت لست جائعا؟
I saw you didn't eat much at the restaurant earlier.
لقد رأيت أنك لم تأكل كثيرًا في المطعم في وقت سابق.
That's why I wanted to have spicy hot pot with you after work.
لهذا السبب أردت أن أتناول معك طبقًا حارًا بعد العمل.
Can you stop caring so much about me?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن الاهتمام بي كثيرًا؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Why are you daydreaming?
لماذا تحلم يقظة؟
The fried dough sticks are mushy.
أصابع العجين المقلية أصبحت طرية.
Didn't we agree on eight seconds?
ألم نتفق على ثماني ثواني؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let me ask you this.
دعني أسألك هذا.
Okay, go ahead.
حسنًا، اذهب للأمام.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
What? What do you want to tell me?
ماذا؟ ماذا تريد أن تقول لي؟
Stop staring. Eat up.
توقف عن التحديق. تناول الطعام.
You'll choke.
سوف تختنق.
What's wrong? Why are you so quiet today?
ما بك؟ لماذا أنت هادئ اليوم؟
Why do you look so down?
لماذا تبدو حزينا هكذا؟
Let me ask you something.
دعني أسألك شيئا.
Is it true that all your girlfriends
هل صحيح أن جميع صديقاتك
never lasted more than three months?
لم تستمر أكثر من ثلاثة أشهر؟
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل؟
Do you like me?
هل أعجبك؟
Answer me first.
أجبني أولا.
I think when two people are dating,
أعتقد أنه عندما يتواعد شخصان،
they should end it at the best moment.
ينبغي عليهم إنهاء الأمر في أفضل وقت.
That's the most beautiful.
هذا هو الأجمل.
Oh.
أوه.
If we kiss, it'll have to last more than three months.
إذا قبلنا، فسوف يستمر الأمر أكثر من ثلاثة أشهر.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدا.
This is the interest for this period.
هذا هو الاهتمام لهذه الفترة.
Sir, here's the money.
سيدي، هنا المال.
- Don't lose it. - Okay.
- لا تفقدها. - حسنًا.
You can take the book if you like it.
يمكنك أن تأخذ الكتاب إذا أعجبك.
Damn.
اللعنة.
I'm impressed.
أنا معجب.
You're still a writer.
مازلت كاتبًا.
"Reconciliation with the Self".
"التصالح مع الذات"
I have a problem.
عندي مشكلة.
I'm always torturing myself.
أنا أعذب نفسي دائمًا.
Looks like I need to read more of this book
يبدو أنني بحاجة لقراءة المزيد من هذا الكتاب
to cultivate my soul.
لتنمية روحي.
Can I have your autograph?
هل يمكنني الحصول على توقيعك؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Don't just reconcile with yourself.
لا تتصالح مع نفسك فقط.
You should pay us back as soon as possible.
ينبغي عليك أن تسدد لنا المبلغ في أقرب وقت ممكن.
It's more important to settle with us.
من المهم أن تستقر معنا.
Look, how about here?
انظر، ماذا عن هنا؟
If I don't get the money the next time I'm here,
إذا لم أحصل على المال في المرة القادمة التي أكون فيها هنا،
I'll take this with me.
سوف آخذ هذا معي.
It's a deal.
إنها صفقة.
Thank you for the book.
شكرا على الكتاب.
Did you come back from abroad recently?
هل عدت من الخارج مؤخرًا؟
Yes, I went to Japan, and then Thailand.
نعم، ذهبت إلى اليابان، ومن ثم إلى تايلاند.
Do you think I'm tanned?
هل تعتقد أنني مدبوغ؟
No, I don't think so.
لا، لا أعتقد ذلك.
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
Yes.
نعم.
Cheers.
هتافات.
I'll treat everyone to a shot.
سأقدم للجميع لقطة.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Let me.
دعني.
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail.
لقد تم تحويل مكالمتك إلى البريد الصوتي.
You will be charged after the beep.
سيتم محاسبتك بعد سماع صوت التنبيه.
[Zhou Xiao Qi: How are you doing?]
[تشو شياو تشي: كيف حالك؟]
[Did those guys harass you again?]
[هل قام هؤلاء الرجال بمضايقتك مرة أخرى؟]
The clinic is closed.
العيادة مغلقة
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Where's Dr. Gu?
أين الدكتور جو؟
He's not here.
إنه ليس هنا.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
New Zealand.
نيوزيلندا.
We're moving to New Zealand for good.
نحن ننتقل إلى نيوزيلندا للأبد.
There's no need to call. He won't answer your calls.
لا داعي للاتصال، فهو لن يجيب على اتصالاتك.
He won't see you again.
لن يراك مرة أخرى
Just give up.
فقط استسلم.
Sorry, the number you dialed is unavailable.
عذراً، الرقم الذي طلبته غير متاح.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Sorry, the number you dialed...
عذرا، الرقم الذي طلبته...
- His phone is with me. - ...is unavailable.
- هاتفه معي. - ...غير متاح.
Please try again later.
يرجى المحاولة مرة أخرى لاحقًا.
Don't glare at me.
لا تحدق في وجهي.
Show yourself out.
اظهر نفسك.
I went to your house. I wanted to tell you...
ذهبت إلى منزلك. أردت أن أخبرك...
Are you going to New Zealand with Fan Yue Jiao?
هل ستذهب إلى نيوزيلندا مع فان يوي جياو؟
She's threatening me with money.
إنها تهددني بالمال.
I'll go with her first.
سأذهب معها أولاً.
I'll try to get the money back.
سأحاول استعادة الأموال.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
If you go, you won't come back.
إذا ذهبت فلن تعود.
It's such a mess now.
لقد أصبحت فوضى الآن.
There's nothing I can do.
لا يوجد شيء أستطيع فعله.
I'll find a way to send you the money I owe you.
سأجد طريقة لإرسال الأموال التي أدين لك بها.
I've never been a choice to you, have I?
لم أكن خيارًا بالنسبة لك أبدًا، أليس كذلك؟
This is the best decision for everyone.
هذا هو القرار الأفضل للجميع.
Please take good care of yourself.
من فضلك اعتني بنفسك جيدا .
Do you love Fan Yue Jiao more than you love me?
هل تحب فان يوي جياو أكثر مما تحبني؟
Is that it?
هل هذا هو؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Is that your answer?
هل هذا جوابك؟
Gu Hou Ze!
قو هو زي!
Why are you out in the rain?
لماذا أنت بالخارج تحت المطر؟
Come in.
ادخل.
Why are you looking for me?
لماذا تبحث عني؟
I have something important to tell you.
عندي شيء مهم أريد أن أخبرك به.
Sit down first.
اجلس أولا.
Xiao Qi.
شياو تشي.
You're pregnant.
أنت حامل.
It was confirmed during the last check-up.
وقد تم تأكيد ذلك خلال الفحص الأخير.
I'm just as shocked as you.
أنا مصدوم مثلك تماما.
I thought we'd need medical technology to have a child.
اعتقدت أننا سنحتاج إلى التكنولوجيا الطبية لإنجاب طفل.
But it really happened.
ولكن هذا حدث بالفعل.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
Xiao Qi, will you marry me?
شياو تشي هل تتزوجيني؟
You can plan the wedding as you please.
يمكنك التخطيط لحفل الزفاف كما يحلو لك.
And I want to give you a grand wedding gift.
وأريد أن أقدم لك هدية زفاف كبيرة.
Just tell me what you want.
فقط أخبرني ماذا تريد.
I'll definitely agree.
سأوافق بالتأكيد.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
When are you leaving?
متى ستغادر؟
This afternoon.
بعد ظهر اليوم.
I want to meet you now.
أريد أن أقابلك الآن.
Your call will be forwarded to voicemail.
سيتم تحويل مكالمتك إلى البريد الصوتي.
You will be charged after the beep.
سيتم محاسبتك بعد سماع صوت التنبيه.
Yue Jiao.
يو جياو.
Why did you let me in here?
لماذا سمحت لي بالدخول هنا؟
Can you do me a favor?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل لي معروفا؟
Can you change into this?
هل يمكنك التحول إلى هذا؟
These are Shu Juan's clothes.
هذه ملابس شو جوان.
Today is the second anniversary of her and Xiao An's passing.
اليوم هو الذكرى الثانية لوفاتها وشياو آن.
I can't believe a car accident
لا أستطيع أن أصدق حادث سيارة
took them both away from me.
أخذهم كلاهما بعيدا عني.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
When Shu Juan was around,
عندما كان شو جوان موجودًا،
we used to go dancing a lot.
كنا نذهب للرقص كثيرًا.
Those days...
تلك الأيام...
were truly wonderful.
لقد كانوا رائعين حقا.
You didn't bring an umbrella again, did you?
لم تحضر معك مظلة مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
I'll give you a ride.
سأوصلك .
You can take my car. I'll give you a ride.
يمكنك أن تأخذ سيارتي، وسأوصلك.
Haven't we decided to be friends?
ألم نقرر أن نكون أصدقاء؟
Please don't keep doing things that'll cause misunderstandings.
من فضلك لا تستمر في فعل الأشياء التي من شأنها أن تسبب سوء الفهم.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
But it's raining heavily.
لكن المطر يهطل بغزارة.
Take my car. I'll give you a ride.
خذ سيارتي، سأوصلك.
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
Get in the car. You're all wet.
ادخل السيارة. أنت مبتل تمامًا.
I want to take the bus.
أريد أن أستقل الحافلة.
Why take the bus when I can drive you?
لماذا تأخذ الحافلة عندما أستطيع أن أقودك؟
I love taking the bus.
أنا أحب ركوب الحافلة.
Your car is uncomfortable.
سيارتك غير مريحة.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Can you stop being so difficult?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن كونك صعبًا جدًا؟
I'm not as casual as you.
أنا لست عاديا مثلك.
I may have only dated for a short time,
ربما كنت أواعد لفترة قصيرة فقط،
but I've never cheated.
ولكنني لم أغش أبدًا.
Isn't that great?
أليس هذا عظيما؟
You only date for three months.
أنت تواعد لمدة ثلاثة أشهر فقط.
It's just a fling.
إنها مجرد علاقة عابرة.
How long do you want it to last?
كم من الوقت تريد أن يستمر؟
Sir.
سيد.
It's normal for relationships to have ups and downs.
من الطبيعي أن تشهد العلاقات صعودًا وهبوطًا.
I'm not someone who needs it to last forever.
أنا لست شخصًا يحتاج إلى أن يدوم إلى الأبد.
Who sets a time limit like that?
من وضع مثل هذا الحد الزمني؟
Then don't set one.
ثم لا تضع واحدا.
Let's just try to be together.
دعونا نحاول أن نكون معًا.
We'll see how long it lasts.
دعونا نرى كم من الوقت سيستمر.
Let's date.
دعونا نتواعد.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
How can you say that so casually?
كيف يمكنك أن تقول ذلك بهذه البساطة؟
Who knows if you're serious or not?
من يعلم إذا كنت جادًا أم لا؟
I'm not made of time.
أنا لست مصنوعًا من الزمن.
Why would I put in so much effort to lie to you?
لماذا أبذل كل هذا الجهد لأكذب عليك؟
So, you're willing to bend your principles for me?
إذن، هل أنت على استعداد للتخلي عن مبادئك من أجلي؟
You seemed really reluctant before.
لقد بدا لك أنك متردد حقًا من قبل.
I was figuring out what I should do.
كنت أفكر في ما يجب أن أفعله.
I thought I'd talk to you when I'd made up my mind.
اعتقدت أنني سأتحدث إليك عندما أتخذ قراري.
Besides, it was so awkward between us.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، كان الأمر محرجًا جدًا بيننا.
How could I speak my mind?
كيف يمكنني أن أعبر عن رأيي؟
You didn't say anything.
لم تقول شيئا.
Of course I'd think you were avoiding me.
بالطبع كنت أعتقد أنك تتجنبني.
I rushed back because I didn't want you to think that way.
لقد عدت مسرعا لأنني لم أردك أن تفكر بهذه الطريقة.
I met some farmers when I was on a business trip in the south.
التقيت ببعض المزارعين عندما كنت في رحلة عمل في الجنوب.
They were growing the flowers they bred.
لقد كانوا يزرعون الزهور التي زرعوها.
The flowers wither in three months.
تذبل الزهور في ثلاثة أشهر.
The farmers also said,
وقال المزارعون أيضا:
"It's better to keep a wonderful past."
"من الأفضل أن نحتفظ بماضي رائع."
When I heard them say that,
عندما سمعتهم يقولون ذلك،
I suddenly felt sad.
لقد شعرت بالحزن فجأة.
That was when I thought of you.
في تلك اللحظة فكرت بك.
I don't think I want to end it in three months with you.
لا أعتقد أنني أريد إنهاء علاقتي معك في ثلاثة أشهر.
It just so happens that it's also three months?
هل حدث أن الأمر استغرق ثلاثة أشهر أيضًا؟
You're bluffing, right?
أنت تخادع، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, I'm bluffing.
نعم، أنا أخادع.
The gist is...
خلاصة الأمر هي...
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
You blabbered on and on...
لقد تحدثت مرارا وتكرارا...
But the summary was way more romantic.
لكن الملخص كان أكثر رومانسية.
So, do you agree?
إذن هل توافق؟
When you promised it'll last more than three months...
عندما وعدت أنها ستدوم أكثر من ثلاثة أشهر...
you didn't mean just four months, right?
لم تقصد أربعة أشهر فقط، أليس كذلك؟
When you turn 40,
عندما تبلغ الأربعين من عمرك،
I'll still celebrate your birthday with you.
سأحتفل بعيد ميلادك معك.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
What?
ماذا؟
Louder, I can't hear you.
أعلى صوتًا، لا أستطيع سماعك.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Happy birthday!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
When you turn 50,
عندما تبلغ الخمسين من عمرك،
I'll still celebrate your birthday with you.
سأحتفل بعيد ميلادك معك.
Happy birthday!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
I've blown out the candles.
لقد أطفأت الشموع.
Can I make a wish now?
هل يمكنني أن أتمنى أمنية الآن؟
What do you want to wish for?
ماذا تريد أن تتمنى؟
Can I stick my tongue in?
هل يمكنني إدخال لساني؟
Xiao Qi, you're so pretty today.
شياو تشي، أنت جميلة جدًا اليوم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
But you'll look prettier if you smile.
لكنك ستبدو أجمل إذا ابتسمت.
I'll smile later.
سأبتسم لاحقا.
What is it that needs to be said in person?
ما هو الشيء الذي يجب أن يقال شخصيا؟
If the debts can be paid off,
إذا كان من الممكن سداد الديون،
will you stay and turn your life upside-down with me?
هل ستبقى وتقلب حياتك رأسا على عقب معي؟
I'm pregnant.
انا حامل.
It's your child.
إنه طفلك
Xiao Qi, we...
شياو تشي، نحن...
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
This is the best solution I've come up with so far.
هذا هو الحل الأفضل الذي توصلت إليه حتى الآن.
Is this another form of revenge?
هل هذا شكل آخر من أشكال الانتقام؟
After I marry him, he'll give me a sum of money.
بعد أن أتزوجه سوف يعطيني مبلغًا من المال.
It can temporarily pay off your debts.
يمكنه سداد ديونك مؤقتًا.
You won't have to leave. You can stay.
لن تضطر إلى المغادرة. يمكنك البقاء.
Stay?
يقضي؟
The marriage is just a show.
الزواج مجرد عرض.
Once your debts are paid off, I'll take our child and leave him.
بمجرد سداد ديونك، سوف آخذ طفلنا وأتركه.
Your idea is too naive.
فكرتك ساذجة جدًا.
It's not an idea.
إنها ليست فكرة.
It's what I've decided.
هذا ما قررته.
Do you like it when I'm so naive?
هل يعجبك عندما أكون ساذجًا جدًا؟
I've never been a choice to you, have I?
لم أكن خيارًا بالنسبة لك أبدًا، أليس كذلك؟
This is the best decision for everyone.
هذا هو القرار الأفضل للجميع.
Fine, Old Wu can give a speech.
حسنًا، يمكن للسيد وو القديم أن يلقي خطابًا.
But even Chairman Fu and Chairman Kang wanted air time.
لكن حتى الرئيس فو والرئيس كانج أرادا الحصول على وقت على الهواء.
They never have anything interesting to say.
لم يكن لديهم أي شيء مثير للاهتمام ليقولوه أبدًا.
What's wrong? Are you tired?
ما بك؟ هل أنت متعب؟
Of course, I've been smiling all day.
بالطبع، لقد كنت مبتسما طوال اليوم.
It's only one day of exhaustion.
إنه يوم واحد فقط من الإرهاق.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you can just relax and be the chairman's wife.
يمكنك فقط الاسترخاء وتكوني زوجة الرئيس.
And have a healthy baby.
ويكون لك طفل سليم.
By the way, I've appointed a driver for you.
بالمناسبة، لقد عينت لك سائقًا.
You're pregnant now. Don't drive.
أنتِ حامل الآن. لا تقودي.
But my job requires me to travel. That'll be inconvenient.
لكن عملي يتطلب مني السفر، وهذا سيكون مزعجًا.
Your status is different now.
حالتك مختلفة الآن.
Driving that small car around?
قيادة تلك السيارة الصغيرة ؟
What would others say about me?
ماذا سيقول الآخرون عني؟
The will and the transfer of trust
الوصية ونقل الثقة
has been amended as per your instructions.
تم تعديله وفقًا لتعليماتك.
Please take a look.
يرجى إلقاء نظرة.
If there are no issues, please sign it.
إذا لم تكن هناك أي مشاكل، يرجى التوقيع عليها.
[Zhan Qian Ren]
[زان تشيان رن]
Thank you, Attorney Ren.
شكرا لك، المحامي رين.
It's my pleasure.
انه لمن دواعي سروري.
Are you going out?
هل انت ستخرج؟
To a consultation.
الى استشارة.
Haven't you been sleeping better lately?
هل لم تنام بشكل أفضل في الآونة الأخيرة؟
You still have sessions?
هل مازال لديك جلسات؟
I'll feel better if I talk to the doctor.
سأشعر بتحسن إذا تحدثت مع الطبيب.
I'm glad it helps.
يسعدني أن هذا يساعد.
Your mood is most important now.
حالتك المزاجية هي الأهم الآن.
Ask the driver to take you.
اطلب من السائق أن يأخذك.
- I'll get going then. - Okay.
- سأذهب إذن. - حسنًا.
Qian Ren got me a driver.
لقد حصل لي تشيان رين على سائق.
I think he wants to keep an eye on us. Be careful.
أعتقد أنه يريد مراقبتنا. كن حذرًا.
I don't know how long this will last.
لا أعلم كم من الوقت سوف يستمر هذا.
Yeah.
نعم.
The baby kicked me.
الطفل ركلني.
That's too soon.
هذا مبكر جداً.
The baby's really kicking me.
الطفل يركلني حقا.
Feel it if you don't believe me.
اشعر بذلك إذا كنت لا تصدقني.
Here.
هنا.
Do you feel it?
هل تشعر به؟
Here. Do you feel it?
هنا هل تشعر به؟
You must've eaten too much ice cream.
لا بد أنك أكلت الكثير من الآيس كريم.
Your stomach is bloated.
معدتك منتفخة.
- It's rumbling. - The baby really kicked me.
- إنه هدير. - لقد ركلني الطفل حقًا.
Why don't you believe me?
لماذا لا تصدقني؟
Yes, I feel it.
نعم أشعر بذلك.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Mr. Zhan asked me to...
لقد طلب مني السيد تشان...
You forgot your phone.
لقد نسيت هاتفك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hello, Dr. Gu. I'm a fan of yours.
مرحباً دكتور جو، أنا من معجبيك.
I've read all your books.
لقد قرأت جميع كتبك.
They encouraged me greatly.
لقد شجعوني كثيرا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Make an appointment with the receptionist for our next session.
حدد موعدًا مع موظف الاستقبال لجلسة العمل القادمة.
Okay.
تمام.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Mr. Zhan said to change the family registry.
قال السيد تشان لتغيير سجل العائلة.
We need your ID and seal.
نحن بحاجة إلى هويتك وختمك.
I asked the driver and he said you were here.
سألت السائق فقال لي أنك هنا.
- That's why I'm here. - Ask me directly next time.
- لهذا السبب أنا هنا. - اسألني مباشرة في المرة القادمة.
Don't ask the driver.
لا تسأل السائق.
Who let you take Shu Juan's stuff?
من سمح لك بأخذ أشياء شو جوان؟
I...
أنا...
Zhan Qian Ren!
زان تشيان رن!